Vivy Vuong

1-(437)-215-5483 - vivyvuong.dev - vngvy48@gmail.com - https://github.com/Vivy24 - https://www.linkedin.com/in/vivy/

About Me

Highly motivated and results-driven computer programming graduate student with a passion to become a good DevOps in the future. With 2 years of experience in customer support and 3 years of programming, I possess a strong understanding of software development and cloud technologies. My passion in coding and cloud development allows me to quickly identify and resolve complex issues, and staying up-to-date with the latest technologies ensures that I can always bring new ideas and solutions to the table. I am eager to join an organization where I can continue to grow and make a significant impact.

Experiences

Customer Support & Data Entry

09/2021 - Present

Vican Multi-Service | Toronto, Ontario

- Proficiently managed inbound inquiries across diverse communication channels including phone, email, and in-person interactions. Resolved customer concerns promptly and comprehensively, ensuring satisfaction and positive experiences.
- Complete assigned data entry tasks promptly and accurately, consistently meeting deadlines.
- Enter more than 200 data forms daily with over 98% correctness, demonstrating efficiency and attention to detail in maintaining data accuracy.

ITS Student Lab Monitor and Hyflex ambassador - Contract

09/2023 - 11/2023

Seneca | Toronto, Ontario

- Proactively monitor computer Lab rooms and e-classrooms prior to session start, to ensure operation readiness and functionality.
- Checking power, verifying basic functionality of computers, touch pads, podium, AV gear, projectors and other devices placed in computer labs and e-classrooms.
- Assisting faculty and professors in resolving technical issues when using computers, touch pads, podium, AV gear, projectors in the assigned campus zone during class time.

System Developer

09/2022 - 04/2023

Healthcare of Ontario Pension Plan - HOOPP | Toronto, Ontario

- Developed and implemented unit tests using Moq and xUnit. Set up a test pipeline in Azure DevOps to enhance code correctness up to 100% and prevent developers pushing broken code into the application.
- Optimized five micro-services by refactoring, separating data, application, and presentation layers for efficient organization of customer documentation during insurance termination.

Web Developer

09/2021 - 06/2022

Seneca VAS | Toronto, Ontario

- Created a web-based application for Vietnamese student to read and contribute Seneca courses using HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Maintained, updated and improved VAS website's UI for event promotion using CSS.

Projects

AWS Data Cloud Storage | AWS Services, ExpressJS, NextJS, Docker

Github Repo | Video Demo

- A web application that allows users upload, access, and handle different types of data fragments: text files, JSON data, and images. Supports transforming data, keeping versions, storing, and searching data efficiently.
- Set up robust CI/CD pipelines for automated tests and deploy through GitHub Actions. Implement unit test in Jest and integration tests in Hurl. Deploy to Docker and integrate with AWS services like ECS, ELB, S3 Bucket, DynamoDB, Cognito and Route 53.

Skills

Technology Skills: Cloud computing (AWS), Programming (C/C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, Python), Linux administration, Software testing, CI/CD workflows (Github Actions), Database design, Web development, Containers, Agile methodologies **Soft Skills**: Complaint Handling, Phone & Online Support, Communication, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Adaptability, Time Management, Trilingual Speaker (English, Vietnamese and Cantonese)

Education, Certifications, and Awards

Seneca College | Advanced Diploma. Computer Programming & Analysis AWS Developer Associate
Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals
Seneca Hackathon Smart Cities 2023 - Finalist
Seneca Hackathon Sustainability 2022 - TDSB Winner

Expected Graduates 05/2024 Expected Issues 03/ 2024 Issued 06/ 2021 Issues 08/ 2023 Issued 02/ 2022